Grandpa, I'm here.
You're just in time.
I read an ancient book last night
and found a prescription
that might help you.
Take one pill from this bottle
every day
for seven days.
No more,
no less.
Got it?
Got it.
Grandpa,
you said there's power in my body.
What kind of power is it?
Why is it sealed?
Girl,
having some power sealed
isn't necessarily a bad thing.
When you're ready,
it will naturally appear.
Until then,
just live well.
That Poison-Repelling Bead is
the Grandmaster's most
treasured possession.
What do you think he would do
if he lost it?
Little snake,
let me give you a name.
Let's call you
Chilian.
How about that?
Grandmaster,
we found a rare herb in the back garden
but can't identify it.
Could you take a look?
Girl, wait here for a moment.
I'll be right back.
Okay, Grandpa.
Huh,
what's this?
What a beautiful bead.
Found it.
How dare you
steal the Grandmaster's
Poison-Repelling Bead!
Steal?
I just saw it here
and picked it up to look at it.
Still trying to argue?
The Poison-Repelling Bead is
the Grandmaster's most precious treasure.
He never takes it off.
You're an outsider.
If you didn't intend to steal it,
how did it end up in your hands?
I just picked it up to look at it.
I had no intention of stealing it.
These two have been
looking at me weirdly from the start.
Is this on purpose?
What happened?
Grandmaster,
this woman stole your
Poison-Repelling Bead.
We saw it with our own eyes.
Yes, we saw it with our own eyes.
Grandpa, I didn't steal it.
I just saw this bead was beautiful
and picked it up to look at it.
Believe it
or not,
I'm just telling the truth.
The look in this girl's eyes
doesn't seem like she's lying.
What are you arguing about?
Oh no, why is the Sect Leader here?
Did he hear what we just said?
Probably not.
As long as we insist she stole it.
As long as we insist.
I see.
You set this up yourselves.
You said
she stole the Poison-Repelling Bead.
Yes,
we saw her pick it up with our own eyes.
Did she put it back
after picking it up?
She did.
But she definitely wanted to steal it.
Then do you know the Poison-Repelling
Pearl has a special property?
What property?
The Poison-Repelling Pearl is forged
from Nine Heavens Black Iron
and Millennium Cold Jade.
It is extremely Yin and cold.
Anyone who touches it
for more than three breaths
will get red frostbite marks
on their palms.
Ah.
Kong has no red marks on her hands.
Instead,
it is your hands that are trembling.